邪恶力量前情提要
Previously on Supernatural.
萨姆
Sammy.
赶快带你弟弟离开屋子 快
Take your brother outside as fast as you can! Go!
爸爸已经踏上了捕猎之旅
Dad's on a hunting trip.
他好几天没回家了
And he hasn't been home in a few days.
这是爸爸的笔记
This was Dad's book.
我想他想让我们继续他的工作
l think he wants us to pick up where he left off.
救助他人 猎杀恶魔 家族事业
Saving people. Hunting things. The family business.
我得找到爸爸 这是现在我唯一想干的
I gotta find Dad. It's the only thing I can think about.
需要多大电流才
What do you got those amped up to?
十万伏特
A hundred thousand volts.
这么强的电流
Damn.
是啊 我想这会那妖怪也感到很爽
I want this Rawhead extra crispy.
记住你得一击即中
Now remember, you only get one shot with these things.
开始干吧
So make it count.
在那里 1… 2… 3
On three. One, two, three.
它还在这里么
Is it still here?
抓住你姐姐的手 跟上
Grab your sister's hand.
我们要离开这里
We're gonna get you out of here.
快走
Let's go.
快 快走
All right, go.
萨姆
Sam!
萨姆 让他们离开这
Sam, get them out of here.
拿着
You take this.
快
Go!
来吧
Come on.
迪恩
Dean!
迪恩 嘿
Dean.Hey.
嘿 嘿
Hey, Hey.
《邪恶力量》
先生 我不得不问下
I'm so sorry to ask.
好象这里没有任何保险的记录
There doesn't seem to be any insurance on file.
是吗 嗯…
Right. Um…
给你
Okay.
伯克威茨先生
Okay, Mr. Burkowitz.
那我们待会在打扰你
Look, we can finish this up later.
没事 没关系的
No, no, it's okay.
我们正好从邻居家穿过
We were just taking a shortcut through the neighborhood…
我们的窗户震碎了
and our windows were down.
当我们走过那房子的时候 听见了尖叫声
and we heard some screaming.
然后就跑了进去
And we stopped, ran in.
然后就发现这个孩子在地下室吗
You found the kids in the basement?
- 是的 - 谢谢你所做的一切
- Yeah. - Well, thank God you did.
不好意思
Excuse me.
没关系
Sure.
谢谢你帮助
Thanks for your help.
- 他还在昏迷吗 - 他在休息
- Hey, doc. Is he? - He's resting.
电击引起的心脏病
The electrocution triggered a heart attack.
相当严重 我恐怕… 。-
Pretty massive, l'm afraid.
他的心脏受到了损伤
His heart, it's damaged.
损伤到什么程度
How damaged?
我们已经尽力了
We've done all we can.
我们现在能让他暂时稳定下来
We can try and keep him comfortable at this point…
但我看他过不了几个礼拜
but I give him a couple weeks at most.
最多一个月
Maybe a month.
不 不 应该还有些其他方法的
No, no, there's gotta be something you can do.
其他的治疗手段
Some kind of treatment.
我们不能指望奇迹 我非常遗憾
can't work miracles. I really am sorry.
以前还没看过白天的电视
Have you ever actually watched daytime TV?
这节目实在太糟了
It's terrible.
我刚才和你的医生谈了下
I talked to your doctor.
泰迪熊软化剂
That fabric softener teddy bear.
噢 我想揍那婊子一顿
Ooh. I'm gonna hunt that little bitch down.
迪恩
Dean.
怎么了
Yeah.
好吧 看来你得扔下我 自己离开这镇子了
All right, well, looks like you're gonna leave town without me.
你在说什么呢 我不会扔下你的
What are you talking about? I'm not gonna leave you here.
你得小心我的车
You're gonna take care of that car.
要不然我发誓做鬼也会缠着你
or I swear I'll haunt your ass.
我觉得这一点也不好笑
l don't think that's funny.
帮个忙 笑一下吧
Ah, come on, it's a little funny.
萨姆 那我该说些什么呢
Look, Sam, what can I say, man?
这是份危险的工作
It's a dangerous gig.
可惜我没法子完成
I drew the short straw.
就是这回事了
That's it, end of story.
别跟我说那样的话 好吗
Don't talk like that, all right?
我们还有其他的选择
We still have options.
什么选择
What options?
土葬还是火葬
You got burial or cremation.
我知道这很难抉择
I know it's not easy…
但是… 我快死了
but l'm gonna die.
但你还得继续
And you can't stop it.
看我的
Watch me.
我是约翰·温彻斯特
This is John Winchester.
我现在无法接电话
I can't be reached.
如果有急事的话 请打个我的儿子迪恩
If this is an emergency, call my son, Dean.
866- 907- 3235
866-907-3235.
他能帮上忙
He can help.
嘿 爸爸 是我 萨姆
Hey, Dad, it's Sam. Uh…
你可能不会听到这个电话 但是 迪恩
You probably won't even get this.
他病了
But it's Dean.
而且医生说他们无计可施
He's sick and the doctor said there's nothing they can do.
他们并不了解我们的所干的事
But they don't know the things we know, right?
别担心 我会想尽一切办法 让他好起来的
So don't worry, because l'm gonna do whatever it takes to get him better.
就这样吧
All right.
只是通知你一声
Just wanted you to know.
你这是在干什么啊
What the hell are you doing here?
我逃了出来
I checked myself out.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
我不会死在一个连个漂亮护士 也没有的医院
I'm not gonna die in a hospital where the nurses aren't even hot.
这才是真的 微笑面对死亡
You know, this whole "I laugh in the face of death" thing…
瞎说 我看根本就不是这回事
it's crap. I can see right through it.
随你怎么说 伙计
Yeah, whatever, dude.
你睡过了吗 你看上去比我还糟
Have you even slept? You look worse than me.
我这三天都在上网
I've been scouring the Internet for the last three days.
寻找一切所有与爸爸日记 里有关的东西
Calling every contact in Dad's journal.
为什么这样做
For what?
为了找到帮你的方法
For a way to help you.
爸爸的一个朋友
One of Dad's friends.
约书亚 他打电话给我
Joshua, he called me back.
告诉我在内布拉斯加州
Told me about a guy in Nebraska.
有一位医学专家
A specialist.
你不会让我就这样安静的死去 是吗
You're not gonna let me die in peace, are you?
我当然不会让你死啦
I'm not gonna let you die, period.
我们走吧
We're going.
- 我帮你 - 我自己来
- I got you. - I got it.
伙计 你还真会吹啊
Man, you're a lying bastard.
你原先说是来看一个医生的
You said we're going to see a doctor.
我是说医学专家
I believe I said a specialist.
他应该就是我们要找的了
This guy's supposed to be the real deal.
真不敢相信你居然让我来看
I can't believe you brought me to see some guy.
这个在帐篷里治病的医生
who heals people out of a tent.
格兰神父是个好人
Reverend Le Grange is a great man.
不错啊
Yeah, that's nice.
我有权抗议
I have a right to protest.
这家伙是个骗子
This man's a fraud.
他在骗取这些人的血汗钱
He's bilking all these people out of their money.
这里就是举行仪式的地方
Sir, this is a place of worship.
我们进去吧
Let's go, move it.
看来人还不少啊
I take it he's not part of the flock.
当人们看见一些无法解释的东西的时候 就产生了争议
When people see what they can't explain, there's controversy.
但萨姆 他是一个信仰医疗学者
But come on, Sam, a faith healer?
可能也是该是时候需要些信仰了
Maybe it's time to have a little faith, Dean.
你知道我信仰什么吗
You know what I got faith in? Reality.
事实 了解正在发生的事
Knowing what's really going on.
看着每天在我们身边的事 你怎么能是个无神论者
How can you be a skeptic with the things we see every day?
没错 我们能看见它们
Exactly. We see them.
我们知道它们是真的存在的
We know they're real.
如果你知道邪恶在那里
If you know evil's out there.
那你怎么能不相信那里也有上帝
How can you not believe good's out there?
因为我也见到过邪恶的东西并 没伤害到人们
l've seen what evil does to good people.
也可能是上帝暗地里干的
Maybe God works in mysterious ways.
可能吧
Maybe he does.
我想你让我对这里产生了兴趣
I think you turned me around on the subject.
是的
Yeah, l'm sure.
我是迪恩 这是萨姆
l'm Dean, this is Sam.
蕾拉
Layla.
既然你并不是信徒 那你来这里干吗
So if you're not a believer, then why are you here?
我兄弟觉得这对我们两个人都好
Well, apparently my brother here believes enough for the both of us.
走吧 蕾拉 快要开始了
Come on, Layla, it's about to start.
好的
All right.
再见
Bye.
我跟你打赌她也是一个信徒
Well, I bet you she can work in some mysterious ways.
和平 友爱 互信
Yeah, peace, love and trust all over.
- 来吧 - 就坐这里吧
- Come on. - Sit right here.
我们坐到前面去
We're sitting up front.
为什么
What? Why?
- 来吧 - 噢 萨姆
- Come on. - Oh, come on, Sam.
你还好吗
You all right?
这真荒谬
This is ridiculous.
我很好
I'm Dude.
伙计 我自己行
Get off me.
就这里吧
Perfect.
好的
Yeah, perfect.
你占了过道
You take the aisle.
每天早上 我妻子苏安 读新闻给我听
Each morning my wife, Sue Ann, reads me the news.
但总没什么好事报导
Never seems good, does it? No.
总是有些人又做了不道德的 坏透了的事
Seems like there's always someone committing some immoral unspeakable act.
但是我可以告诉你 上帝正监视着我们
But I say to you God is watching. Yes, he is.
上帝会奖励那些好人 同时也会惩罚那些坏蛋
God rewards the good and he punishes the corrupt.
朋友们正是上帝保佑着这里
It is the Lord who does the healing here, friends.
挑选接受治疗的人
The Lord who guides me in choosing who to heal…
上帝帮助我看穿人心来
by helping me see into people's hearts.
阿门
Amen.
阿门 又或者伸向他们的钱包
Yeah, or into their wallets.
你也是怎么想的吗 年轻人
You think so, young man?
对不起
Sorry.
不 不必了
No, no, don't be.
在瞎子面前说话你得小心点
Watch what you say around a blind man.
我们的耳朵还真不赖
We got real sharp ears.
你叫什么名字
What's your name, son?
- 迪恩 - 迪恩
- Dean. - Dean.
我想请你到我这里来
I want you to come up here with me.
迪恩 继续
Dean, go on.
不 不用了
It's okay.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
你到这里不就是想痊愈吗
You've come here to be healed, haven't you?
是的 没错 但…
Well, yeah, but.
你可以叫其他人上去
Maybe you should just pick someone else.
并不是我选择了你 是上帝选择了你
No, I didn't pick you, Dean, the Lord did.
去吧
Get up there.
去吧…
Yes…
赞美主 阿门
Praise the Lord, amen.
准备好了吗
You ready?
听着 我并不想冒犯你
Yeah, look, no disrespect…
但我并不是一个信徒
but l'm not exactly a believer.
孩子 你会是的
You will be, son.
你会是的
You will be.
朋友们让我们一起祈祷
Pray with me, friends.
没事了
All right now.
迪恩
Dean!
说话呀
Say something.
你现在真的感觉好了吗
So you really feel okay?
我很好 萨姆
I feel fine, Sam.
根据你的测试报告 你的心脏没有问题了
Well, according to all your tests there's nothing wrong with your heart.
没有任何迹象表明它之前有问题
No sign there ever was.
象你这年纪应该不会有心脏问题
Not that a man your age should have heart trouble…
但仍然很奇怪 确有这样的事发生
but still, it's strange. Does happen.
你说的奇怪是什么意思
What do you mean, strange?
就在昨天 一个和你年纪相仿的年轻人
Just yesterday, a young guy like you.
一个27岁的运动员死于心脏病
27, athletic. Out of nowhere, heart attack.
谢谢 医生
Thanks, doc.
不客气
No problem.
有点不对劲
That's odd.
可能只是巧合
Maybe it's a coincidence.
人的心脏随时都可能出问题
People's hearts give out all the time.
不 并不是这样的
No, they don't.
难道还真的要吹毛求疵不成
Do we have to look this one in the mouth?
我们为什么不能谢谢那个救你的人呢
Why can't we be thankful the guy saved your life and move on?
因为我无法逃避这种感觉
Because I can't shake this feeling, that's why.
什么样的感觉
What feeling?
当我痊愈的时候 我感到有些不对劲
When I was healed, I just I felt wrong.
我感到冷 虽然就一秒
I felt cold and for a second.
我看见那个老人
I saw someone, this old man.
我告诉你 萨姆他是个幽灵
I'm telling you, it was a spirit.
如果真的是那样
If there was something there.
我想我也应该能看见
I would've seen it too.
我只看到非常难堪的场面罢了
I've been seeing an awful lot of things lately.
打断一下
Oh, well, excuse me, psychic wonder.
你得相信我
You're gonna need a little faith.
萨姆 我捕猎这么久了 足以深信这种感觉
Sam, l've been hunting long enough to trust a feeling like this.
那好吧
Yeah, all right.
那你想怎么样
So, what do you want to do?
为什么不去看下 那个发心脏病的家伙
Check out the heart-attack guy.
我真想去拜访那神父
I'm gonna visit the Reverend.
我感觉棒极了
I feel great.
但我想了解下 到底发生了什么
Just trying to, you know, make sense of what happened.
奇迹发生了而已
A miracle is what happened.
奇迹经常在罗伊身边发生
Miracles come so often around Roy.
什么时候开始的
When did they start.
那所谓的奇迹
The miracles?
有一天我醒来瞎了
Woke up one morning stone blind.
医生说我得了癌症 告诉我还有一个月的命
Doctors figured out I had cancer, told me I had maybe a month.
因此我祈祷出现奇迹
So we prayed for a miracle.
我那时很虚弱 但和Sue说
I was weak, but I told Sue Ann.
你要坚持不懈的祈祷
"You just keep right on praying."
接着我昏迷了
I went into a coma.
医生说我可能再也不会醒过来 但我苏醒过来了
Doctors said I wouldn't wake up, but I did…
癌症也随之而去
and the cancer was gone.
如果这事不是这几年发生的话
If it wasn't for these eyes.
还真没有人会相信有这回事
No one would believe I'd ever had it.
然后你就能治疗其他的人了吗
And suddenly you could heal people.
我后来发现的确是这样
I discovered it afterwards, yes.
上帝一直保佑着我
God's blessed me in many ways.
他的追随者日夜增多
And his flock just swelled overnight.
这还只是个开始
And this is just the beginning.
我能问你个问题吗
Can I ask you one last question?
当然可以
Of course you can.
为什么 为什么是我
Why? Why me?
不管其他病人救助我 为什么
Out of all the sick people, why save me?
正如我刚才所说的 是上帝指引了我
Well, like I said before, the Lord guides me.
我看穿了你的心 而你也正好从人群中站了出来
I looked into your heart and you just stood out from all the rest.
你从我的心中看到了些什么
What did you see in my heart?
一个有远大目标的年轻人 想干一翻事业
A young man with an important purpose, a job to do…
但还没完成
and it isn't finished.
我告诉你 他看上去很健康 每天都游泳
Telling you, he seemed healthy. Swam every day.
不吸烟 所以他得心脏病 比较奇怪
Didn't smoke. You know, so a heart attack just kind of seemed bizarre.
根据你所说的他病倒的 那天还正在跑步吗
You said he was running right before he collapsed.
是的 他很奇怪
Yeah, yeah, he was freaking out.
说有些东西正跟着他
Said that something was after him.
他都说了些什么
Did he say what?
不太清楚
Well, thin air is what.
好象没说什么
I mean, there wasn't anything.
那好吧 谢谢
All right, thanks.
嘿 伙计 你的钟坏了
Hey, buddy, your clock's busted.
是啊 好象不走了
Oh, yeah, we can't get it working.
在4 17冻住了
It just froze at 4:1 7.
马歇尔就是那个时候死的吗
Is that the same time Marshall died?
你怎么知道的
How'd you know?
- 迪恩 - 嘿 - 感觉怎么样
- Dean, hey. - Hey. - How are you feeling?
我很好 我想应该已经痊愈了
l feel good. Cured, I guess.
你来这干吗
What are you doing here?
我母亲
You know, my mom…
她想和神父谈谈
she wanted to talk to the Reverend.
蕾拉
Layla.
我又来了
Yes, we're here again.
对不起 罗伊正在休息
Oh, l'm sorry, but Roy's resting.
他现在不接见任何人
He won't be seeing anyone else right now.
苏安 帮帮忙吧
Sue Ann, please.
这是我们第6次来了 他应该接见我们
This is our sixth time. He's got to see us.
罗伊也知道蕾拉的状况
Roy's well aware of Layla's situation.
只要上帝允许他肯定愿意帮助你们
and he very much wants to help…just as soon as the Lord allows.
相信我 洛克太太
Have faith, Mrs. Rourke.
你干吗还在这里
Why are you still even here?
你已经得到你想要的了
You got what you wanted.
妈妈 不要说了
Mom, stop.
蕾拉这太过分了
No, Layla, this is too much.
我们去过所有的地方了
We've been to every single service.
如果罗伊还是选择其他陌生人而不是你
If Roy would stop choosing these strangers over you…
他们根本就不是信徒
strangers who don't even believe.
我已经非常至诚的祈祷了
I just can't pray any harder.
蕾拉 到底怎么了
Layla, what's wrong?
我有病
I have this thing.
是脑瘤
It's a brain tumor.
而且无法动手术
It's inoperable.
在六个月内 医生说…
In six months, the doctors say…
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
没事的
It's okay.
胡说
No, it isn't.
为什么你能活的比我女儿长
Why do you deserve to live more than my daughter?
你发现了什么
What did you find out?
我很抱歉
l'm sorry.
为什么道歉
Sorry about what?
马歇尔死于4 17
Marshall Hall died at 4:1 7.
正是我痊愈的时间
The exact time I was healed.
是的 因此我把痊愈的人放在一起
Yeah.So I put together a list.
这些受罗伊治疗去年一共六个人
Reverend Roy's healed six people over the past year…
然后我核对了当时当地的讣告
and I checked them with the local obits.
每次有人痊愈 就有人死亡
Every time someone was healed, someone else died.
每次受害者都死于与被治愈者 相同的病症
And each time the victim died of the same symptom Le Grange was healing.
有些人癌症被治愈 而有些人却死于癌症
Someone's healed of cancer, someone else dies of cancer?
洛克·格兰奇正在用一个生命 换另一个生命
Somehow Le Grange is trading a life for another.
有人吗
Hello?
等等
Wait, wait, wait.
所以马歇尔的死就是为了救我
So Marshall Hall died to save me?
迪恩 他也可能死于其他的方式
Dean, the guy probably would've died anyway…
而也有人因此被治愈
and someone else would've been healed.
你不该带我去那里
You never should have brought me here.
迪恩 我只是想救你的命
Dean, I was just trying to save your life.
萨姆 那个人是因我而死的
But, Sam, some guy is dead now because of me.
我不关心这个
I didn't know.
朋友们和我一起祈祷
Pray with me, friends.
我不了解这些罗伊是如何做到的
The thing I don't understand is, how is Roy doing it?
如何以命换命
How's he trading a life for a life?
并不是他干的
Roy is not doing it.
而是其他人替他干的
Something else is doing it for him.
什么意思 在舞台上的那个老人
do you mean? The old man I saw on-stage.
我不相信这些表面现象 但我却知道这背后是什么
l didn't want to believe it, but I knew it.
你在说些什么啊
What are you talking about?
只有一种生物能这样夺走生命
Only one thing can give and take life like that.
我们正面对这一个死神
We're dealing with a reaper.
你真的认为那是死神吗
You really think it's the Grim Reaper…
就象毁灭天使 吸取你的灵魂
like, Angel of Death, collect your soul, the whole deal?
并不是这种死神 是另外种
No, no, no, not the Reaper, a reaper.
每种不同的文化里的死神都不一样
There's reaper lore in every culture on earth.
他们有一百多种不同的名字
Go by different names.
每个可能有不只一个名字
It's possible there's more than one of them.
你说你看见一个套状的家伙
You said you saw a dude in a suit.
你觉得他就和里面的角色一样吗
What, he should've been working the black robe thing?
你说那个钟停止不走了 是吗
You said it yourself that the clock stopped.
死神停止了时间
Reapers stop time.
只有他来到你身边你才能见到他
You can only see them when they're coming at you…
这就是为什么我可以看见 而你不行
which is why I could see it.
- 可能吧 - 除此之外也没其他可能了
- Maybe. - There's nothing else it could be, Sam.
问题是 罗伊是怎么办到的
The question is, how's Roy controlling the thing?
十字架
That cross.
什么
What?
那有个十字架
There was this cross.
我注意到了那个教堂
I noticed it in the church tent.
我想我以前在哪里见到过
I knew l'd seen it before.
在这
Here.
塔罗牌
A tarot?
这就对了
lt makes sense.
塔罗牌要追溯到公元早期
Tarot dates back to the early Christian era…
当有一些牧师在使用魔法 …
when priests were using magic and.
而另外一些则成了恶魔的奴仆
a few veered into the dark stuff.
产生了巫术和
Necromancy and how to push death away.
如何长生不死
How to cause it.
那就是说罗伊于死神用黑魔法 签下了契约
So Roy's using black magic to bind the reaper.
如果是那样的话 那就没人能收拾他了
If he is, he's riding the whirlwind.
就象带着项圈的狗无人看管
Like putting a dog leash on a great white.
那好吧 我们来阻止他
Okay, then we stop Roy.
怎么阻止
How?
你该知道的
You know how.
你又在瞎说什么呢
What the hell are you talking about?
我们不能杀了罗伊
We can't kill Roy.
那家伙正扮演着上帝
Sam, the guy's playing God.
决定人的生死
He's deciding who lives and dies.
但对我来说只是个妖怪
That's a monster.
不 我们不能杀人 迪恩
No, we're not gonna kill a human being, Dean.
如果我们那样做 我们比他也好不到那里去
We do that, we're no better than he is.
那好吧 我们不杀罗伊
Okay, so we can't kill Roy.
我们不杀死人 还有其他的点子吗
We can't kill death. Any bright ideas, college boy?
如果罗伊用符咒控制着死神
Okay, if Roy's using some kind of black spell on the reaper…
我们得找出如何破解掉它
we gotta figure out what it is and how to break it.
如果罗伊是用的符咒 那可能有符咒书
If Roy's using a spell, there might be a spell book.
看看你能不能找到
See if you can find it.
加紧了
Hurry up too.
仪式在15分钟内要开始了
Service starts in 1 5 minutes.
我试着拖住罗伊
I'll try to stall Roy.
洛克·格兰奇是个骗子
Roy Le Grange is a fraud.
他不是治病术士
He's no healer.
阿门 伙计
Amen, brother.
加油 继续干
You keep up the good work.
谢谢
Thank you.
你发现了什么
What do you got?
罗伊选择那些他认为不道德的人 作为受害者
Roy's choosing victims he sees as immoral.
我想我已经知道下一个会是谁了
And I think I know who's next on his list.
还记得那个抗议者吗
Remember that protestor?
- 在停车厂的那个家伙吗 - 是的
- In the parking lot? - Yeah.
是的 我会找到他 但你不要让罗伊治疗任何人 好吗
Yeah, l'll find him. But you can't let Roy heal anyone, all right?
蕾拉 蕾拉·洛克 到这里来 孩子
Layla. Layla Rourke. Come up here, child.
- 妈妈 谢谢你 - 我爱你
- Mom. Thank you. - I love you.
哦 伙计
Oh, man.
蕾拉听我说
Layla, listen to me.
你不能去那里
You can't go up there.
为什么不
Why not?
我们为此都等了几个月了
We've waited for months.
你不能让罗伊治疗你
You can't let Roy heal you.
我不明白
I don't understand.
但罗伊治愈了你 不是吗
Roy healed you, didn't he?
那我为什么不能让他试试
Why won't you at least let him try?
因为如果你这样做 一些不好的事就会发生
If you do, something bad is gonna happen.
我无法解释 但我希望你能相信我
I can't explain. I just need to you believe me.
- 蕾拉 - 不要去
- Layla. - Please.
对不起
l'm sorry.
蕾拉 蕾拉
Layla Layla.
亲爱的
Dear child.
这是你应得的
You deserve this.
上帝终于最后选择了你
I knew the Lord was planning.
我知道只是时间的问题而已
I knew it was just a matter of time.
救救我
Help!
朋友们与我一起祈祷
Pray with me, friends.
我希望你准备好了
l hope you're ready.
我准备好了
I am.
救救我 求你了
Help! Help me, please!
他在哪里
Where is he?
就在这里
It's right there!
跟我来
Fine, come on.
着火拉 教堂着火拉
Fire! Hurry! Tent's on fire!
大家敢快离开这里
Fire! Everybody get out of here!
不要 求你不要离开
No. No, please.
别离开 求你了
Please don't stop. Please?
神父 求你不要停止
Reverend, please, please. Please don't stop. Please!
朋友们 大家请按秩序离开
Friends, if you'd all just leave the tent in an orderly fashion…
我们会处理这里所发生的事
and we'll figure out what's going on out there and we'll come back.
我办到了 我拖住了他
l did it. I stopped Roy.
大卫… 我想应该没事了
David, I think it's okay.
- 不 - 迪恩 这仍然无效
- No. - Dean, it didn't work.
死神还是来了
The reaper's still coming.
我跟你讲
I'm telling you.
我早就跟你讲过了
I'm telling you, it must not have worked.
这并不是罗伊控制的
Roy must not be controlling this thing.
那是谁
Well, then who the hell is?
苏安
Sue Ann.
帮帮我 帮帮我
Help! Help me!
救命啊
Help!
你没事了 你没事了
I got you. I got you.
感谢上帝
Thank God.
我不明白
I just don't understand.
我们为你做了那么多 罗伊治愈了你
After everything we've done for you, after Roy healed you.
我们非常非常失望 迪恩
I'm just very, very disappointed, Dean.
你们可以让他走了
You can let him go.
我不会起诉他的
I'm not gonna press charges.
上帝会对付他 因为他是合适的
The Lord will deal with him as he sees fit.
要是让我们在抓到你
We catch you around here again.
别怪我们对你不客气
We'll put the fear of God in you, understand?
是的 我明白了
Yes, sir, fear of God. Got it.
蕾拉
Layla.
为什么你要那么做
Why would you do that, Dean?
这可能是我唯一的机会
And it could have been my only chance.
他不是治病术士
He's not a healer.
但他治愈你了
He healed you.
我知道这可能不公平
I know it doesn't seem fair.
我希望我能解释
and I wish I could explain…
但可惜罗伊并不是我要的答案 很遗憾
but Roy is not the answer, I'm sorry.
再见 迪恩
Goodbye, Dean.
我希望你好运
I wish you luck.
我是真心的
I really do.
你也是
Same to you.
你应该比我好运
You deserved a lot more than me.
今晚单独会议 不会有打扰了
Private session tonight, no interruptions.
我向你保证
I give you my word,
我会治愈你的女儿
I'll heal your daughter.
谢谢 神父
Thank you, Reverend.
愿上帝保佑你
God bless you.
所以罗伊就深信不疑
So Roy really believes.
我想他还了解他妻子的所为
I don't think he has any idea what his wife's doing.
我发现这被藏在图书馆里
Well, I found this hidden in their library.
很巧 这正是一个投奔恶魔 的牧师所写的
It's ancient. Written by a priest who went dark side.
有一种符咒用来捕获死神
There's a binding spell in here for trapping a reaper.
可能是种毒咒
Must be a hell of a spell.
是的 你得用骨头 人血建造一个
Yeah. You gotta build a black altar with seriously dark stuff Bones.
黑暗祭坛
human blood.
象这样画个叉
To cross a line like that.
那神父的妻子是个黑魔法师
That preacher's wife…Black magic, murder. Evil.
因为丈夫正奄奄一息
Desperate.
不顾一切的
Her husband was dying.
想要救回他
She would've done anything to save him.
他用符咒让死神远离罗伊 坦白的说就是
She was using the binding spell to keep the reaper away from Roy.
逃脱死亡
Cheating death, literally.
但既然罗伊没死 那她为什么还要继续使用这符咒
Yeah, but Roy's alive, so why's she still using the spell?
没错
Right.
为了迫使死神杀死那些那些 她认为不道德的人
To force the reaper to kill people she thinks are immoral.
那些认为他们在做好事的人们 认为是上帝救了我们
May God save us from half the people who think they're doing God's work.
我们得解除那个符咒
We gotta break that spell, Dean.
苏安有一个象这样的科普特十字架
Sue Ann had a Coptic cross like this. Once she dropped it…
当十字架掉落的时候 死神就退走了
the reaper backed off.
所以你认为我们得找到它 或者摧毁那个祭坛吗
So you think we gotta find the cross or destroy the altar?
可能两者都要
Maybe both?
不管怎么样 我们得快点行动
Whatever we do, we'd better do it soon.
罗伊今晚要治疗蕾拉
Roy's healing Layla tonight.
这是蕾拉的车
That's Layla's car.
她已经到了
She's already here.
是的
Yeah. Dean…
如果罗伊选择了用我 来交换蕾拉
If Roy picked Layla instead of me…
那她应该现在正在接受治疗
she'd be healed right now.
迪恩 别那样说
Dean, don't.
如果她今天没治愈的话
And if she's not healed tonight.
几个月内她就会死亡
She's gonna die in a couple months.
这对她来说是非常可怕的
What's happening to her is horrible…
那你想怎么样
but what are you gonna do?
让其他人的死来救她吗
Let somebody else die to save her?
你自己说过的 迪恩 你不是上帝
aid it yourself, You can't play God.
过来 请大家过来
Gather around. Please, everyone gather around.
接近 上来吧
Come in closer, come on up.
苏安在哪里
Where's Sue Ann?
房子里
House.
去找苏安 我会跟上你的饿
Go find Sue Ann. l'll catch up.
你想干什么…
What are you?
嘿 你们不是想对我不客气吗
Hey. Gonna put that fear of God in me?
看见他了吗
See him?
没
No.
杂种狗
Psycho mutt.
我给了你兄弟的命
I gave your brother life.
也可以取走它
and I can take it away.
萨姆 你不明白吗
Sam, can't you see?
上帝选择了我来惩恶扬善
The Lord chose me to reward the just and punish the wicked…
你兄弟是邪恶的
and your brother is wicked…
他是该死的 就象蕾拉应该活下来一样
and he deserves to die just as Layla deserves to live.
这是上帝的意愿
It's God's will.
再见了 萨姆
Goodbye, Sam.
洛克太太
Mrs. Rourke.
现在和我一起祈祷
Pray with me now.
朋友们和我一起祈祷
Pray with me, friends.
没事了
All right now.
咒语
[CHANTING lN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
哦
Oh!
我不明白
l don't understand.
我没感觉有什么不同啊
I don't feel different.
我的天那
My God.
你都干了些什么
What have you done?
他不是你的上帝
He's not your God.
神父
Reverend?
苏安吗
Sue Ann?
你没事吧
You okay?
什么鬼日子
Hell of a week.
是啊
Yeah.
来吧
All right, come on.
我们该走了
We should get going.
那是什么
What is it?
没什么
Nothing.
什么东西
What is it?
我们做的是对的吧 是吗
We did the right thing here, didn't we?
当然
Of course we did.
感觉还是不太好
It doesn't feel like it.
我去开
I got it.
嘿 蕾拉 进来吧
Hey, Layla, come on in.
嘿
Hey.
你怎么知道我们在这里
Hey. How did you know we were here?
萨姆打电话给我
Sam called.
他说你想道个别
He said you wanted to say goodbye.
我想… 要瓶苏打水
I'm gonna grab a soda.
你们想去那里
So where are you going?
还不知道
Oh, don't know yet.
我们这活要到处跑
Our work kind of takes us all over. So…
我去看过了罗伊
You know, I went back to see Roy.
怎么了
What happened?
没什么
Nothing.
他用手放在我的额头上
I mean, he laid his hands on my forehead.
但什么都没发生
But nothing happened.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉那没生效
I'm sorry it didn't work.
苏安
And Sue Ann…
她死了
She's dead, you know?
中风
Stroke.
是的 我听说了
Yeah, I heard.
罗伊是个好人
You know, Roy's a good man.
他不该有这下场
He doesn't deserve what's happened.
太残忍了…
It must be rough.
对一些东西深信不疑 但结果却让他如此失望
to believe in something so much and have it disappoint you like that.
你没听到一些奇怪的事吗
You wanna hear something weird?
什么
Hmm?
我没事了 真的
I'm okay. Really.
我想如果即使你是信徒的话
I guess if you're gonna have faith…
当奇迹出现你也不能把它当作是信念始然
you can't just have it when the miracles happen.
平时还是需要些信仰的
You have to have it when they don't.
那现在又如何了呢
So, what now?
上帝总是在暗地里
God works in mysterious ways.
再见 迪恩
Goodbye, Dean.
嘿
Hey…
你了解的 我不经常祈祷
You know, I'm not much of the praying type…
但我会为你祈祷
But l'm gonna pray for you.
没想到奇迹那么快就出现了
Well…there's a miracle right there.